We have our settings screen but no settings.
我们的应用有设置界面但是没有设置选项
In the next several sections you're going to be adding our two settings.
在接下来的几个阶段，你将会在我们的应用中添加两个设置选项
I'll walk you through how we add our first setting for
我将会带你学习如何添加地理位置，作为应用的第一个设置选项
location, then you'll do the temperature setting on your own, so listen closely.
紧接着你将自己动手添加温度的设置选项，所以接下来请仔细听讲
First we design a preference XML file.
首先我们设计一个界面 XML文件
The root element should be a preference screen.
根节点需是一个preferencescreen
In this example we have a check box preference and
在这个例子中，我们的应用中有一个checkboxpreference
a list preference inside of it.
和一个listpreerence
In order to add the preferences XML file to our app,
为了在应用中添加一个preferences XML文件，
we first need to create an XML folder under the resources res directory.
首先我们需要在资源目录下创建一个XML文件夹
Right-click on the res folder, go to new Android resource directory and
在资源文件夹上点击右键，选择新建Android resource directory
then type in XML as the name of the directory.
接着输入XML作为目录的名字
For resource type you can use XML and then hit OK.
对于资源类型你可以选择XML，然后点击OK
Inside this folder, we right-click to create a new XML resource file.
在这个文件夹下，我们点击右键创建一个新的XML资源文件
We call it pref_general,
我们称之为pref_general
and the root element is a preference screen as we saw on the developer's site.
根节点就是preference，就像我们在开发者这边看到的一样
And then our preferences file is created.
这样我们的preferences文件就创建完成了
Then add the location preference.
然后增添我们的地址首选项
Since the wireframes showed an editable text field to input user location as
由于线框里面需要显示一个可用来输入用户地理位置的字符串
a string, we make this an EditTextPreference.
我们将使用EditTextPreference来进行编码
If you want to learn more about all the possible XML attributes,
如果你想学习更多有关 XML 的其他属性
you can google for EditTextPreference.
你可以 Google 一下 EditTextPreference
First we specify a title for
首先我们为preference指定一个标题
the preference which will be the label that's displayed to the user.
将用是这个preference向用户展示的标签
Then we specify a key.
然后我们指定一个key
And this key is actually the key value in SharedPreferences.
而这个key实际上就是SharedPreferences的key value
Going back to the code, we also add these attributes to describe the Edit Text
回到代码中，我们增加了一些属性，用来描述一些在线框中显示的
field in the pop up dialog that was shown in the wire frames.
对话框中的EditText
Going back to the code, we can also configure properties of the Edit Text field.
在代码中，我们也可以编辑 Edit Text field 的属性
We specify the input type to be text, and we cap it to a single line of text.
我们指定输入类型为text，并且设置为单行显示文本
It's bad practice to hard code these strings here,
在这里硬编码这些字符串是不好的编码习惯
so we declare them as constants in the strings.XML file.
所以我们把它们定义为string.xml文件中的常量
These are the strings we declared.
这就是我们定义的字符串
This is the name of the label of the preference.
这是preference标签的名字
It's user-visible, so we add a char limit for translation purposes.
这是用户可见的，为了转义我们增加了字符限制
You also specify location which is the name of the key in Shared Preferences.
你也可以指定那个在Sharepreferences中被命名为location的key
We don't want to translate it because we always want to find the key based
我们并不翻译它因为我们经常通过这个名字
on this name.
寻找 key
We also specify a constant for the default location.
我们也可以指定一个常量作为默认的location
We also don't translate this because we need to send it to the server API
我们这里也不翻译它因为我们需要将它输送给 server API
like this.
就像这样
When you're done with these steps check them off and continue
当你把这些步骤都做完了的时候，将下面的选项勾选，并继续